templatesblock.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy | Templates Block

## Privacy Policy

[Updated April 24, 2015]

for http://www.templatesblock.com/

The privacy of our visitors to http://www.templatesblock.com/ is important to us.

At http://www.templatesblock.com/, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use or visit http://www.templatesblock.com/, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable or any other), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Firefox or any other), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Most of the such data is collected by Google Analytics which we use to provide the best possible browsing experience of our website.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. Confidential information such as IDs, passwords, accounts, etc are not even touched.

**Really Simple Syndication**  
The information provided by you [such as Emails and subscription requests] is only used for the purpose of providing it to feedburner to provide you with latest updates from our blog. Your information is neither used by us for our own purpose nor transferred or sold to any third party.

**Advertising and Sponsorship**  
The information provided to us by our advertisers or sponsors is not sold to any third party, Information such emails and names are strictly used by us only to communicate with our advertisers or sponsors.
